(birds chirping)
♪♪
♪ Aaah aaah aaah ♪
♪ Well, it's been
building up inside of me ♪
♪ For oh, I don't
know how long ♪
♪ I don't know why ♪
♪ But I keep thinking ♪
♪ Something's
bound to go wrong ♪
♪ But she looks in my eyes ♪
♪ And makes me realize ♪
♪ And she says ♪
♪ Don't worry, baby ♪
♪ Everything will
turn out all right ♪
♪ Don't worry, baby ♪
♪ I guess I should've
kept my mouth shut ♪
♪ When I started to
brag about my car ♪
♪ But I can't back down now ♪
♪ Because I pushed the
other guys too far ♪
♪ She makes me come alive ♪
♪ And makes me want to drive ♪
♪ When she says ♪
♪ Don't worry, baby ♪
♪ Everything will
turn out all right ♪
♪ Don't worry, baby ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ♪
♪♪
♪ She told me ♪
♪ Baby, when you race today ♪
♪ Just take along
my love with you ♪
♪ And if you knew how
much I loved you ♪
♪ Baby, nothing could
go wrong with you ♪
♪ Oh, what she does to me ♪
♪ When she makes love to me ♪
♪ And she says ♪
♪ Don't worry, baby ♪
♪ Everything will
turn out all right ♪
♪ Don't worry, baby ♪
♪ Everything will
turn out all right ♪
♪ Don't worry, baby ♪
(birds chirping)